# Waqas Rasheed

Caring and motivated teacher with 2 years of class room experience. Online tutor with 3 years experience in different countries of the world specially in United state. Proficient in English instruction and individualized education plans. Looking to contribute my knowledge and skills in an education department



waqas.email1@gmail.com

03424500342



Q Lahore, Pakistan

#### **EDUCATION**

MSCS (Evening Time) **UET, Lahore** 

09/2019 - Present

**BSCS** 

GCU, Lahore

11/2014 - 05/2018

3.22/4

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Lecturer

Leads group of colleges

08/2018 - Present

Head of computer science Department

I have been teaching at I.C.S, B.sc and M.Sc (I.T) classses with following subject

- Introduction to computing
- Programming fundamental with C and C++
- Object oriented programming with JAVA
- Operating system
- Database with SQL
- Digital logic and Design

#### Internee

Oratier Technology, Lahore

06/2018 - 09/2018 Asp.net MVC developer

### **SKILLS**





SDLC



Microsoft Office

# **FINAL YEAR PROJECT**

http://alrazihealthcare.com/ (09/2018 – Present) (09/2018 - Present)

 I have earned A+ in my final year project under Head of Computer science department at GCU, Lahore Sir Prof Dr. Syed Asad Raza Kazmi supervisor and my project has published online.

## **CERTIFICATE**

Internship in Asp.net

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

Professional Working Proficiency

Urdu

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### **INTERESTS**

Coding

Reading English Grammer book

Problem solving